{
    "subject": "resource/A_Buffalope's_Tale",
    "predicate": "property/mediaType",
    "object": "Print",
    "human_readable": "The media type of A Buffalope's Tale is Print.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9620205760002136,
            "question": "What is the media type of A Buffalope's Tale?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8932421803474426,
            "question": "What other types of media could A Buffalope's Tale be presented in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7776155471801758,
            "question": "Does the print format affect how people experience the story of A Buffalope's Tale?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7326213717460632,
            "question": "Is A Buffalope's Tale available in digital format?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6233742237091064,
            "question": "Could you find a physical copy of A Buffalope's Tale at a library?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4773795008659363,
            "question": "What other books might be published in the same format as A Buffalope's Tale?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.06457505375146866,
            "question": "How does the physical appearance of a print book contribute to its appeal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.05817372351884842,
            "question": "Can you name other popular books that are primarily published in print format?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.04267428442835808,
            "question": "What is the typical lifespan of a printed book?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.030582576990127563,
            "question": "Are there any advantages to reading a book in print format?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The media type of A Buffalope's Tale is Print.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2133_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the typical lifespan of a printed book?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2133_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name other popular books that are primarily published in print format?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2133_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does the physical appearance of a print book contribute to its appeal?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2133_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2133_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2133_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2133_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2133_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2133_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2133_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2133_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2133_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2133_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2133_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents mention \"A Buffalope's Tale\" and describe it as a book, implying that the media type is print."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided text mentions that the first chapter of \"A Buffalope's Tale\" can be read on Sebastian Darke's official website, implying a digital format.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}